<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>米歇尔的虚拟口袋</title>
        <link>http://michtintin.com/zh-cn/</link>
        <description>This is my cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 11:59:24 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="http://michtintin.com/zh-cn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Fishcake-1</title>
    <link>http://michtintin.com/zh-cn/posts/fishcake-1/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 11:59:24 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>michtintin</author>
    <guid>http://michtintin.com/zh-cn/posts/fishcake-1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Transforming pure fish into cakes by hand using spanish mackerels, salt and pepper. No additives just pure fish. Hi! There. Do you wanna learn how to make fish cakes by hand? Today we&rsquo;re going to show you just that. It&rsquo;s a very common ingredient in flat noodles, fried rice, noodles, fish soup noodles in Singapore and Malaysia. Not all types of mackerels are suitable to make fish cakes some don&rsquo;t hold up to their firmness and tend to be powdery so make sure you pick one with spotted skin and request the fishmonger to fillet it for you if I&rsquo;m not wrong it&rsquo;s called Japanese/ Spanish mackerels and before I start working on the fish cakes it&rsquo;s best to line the table with a layer of thick newspaper so that it&rsquo;s easier to clean later the other two ingredients you need are salt and white grounded pepper you also need a saline solution with a ratio of one teaspoon to a cup of water dip your spoon into the saline solution and gently start scraping from the top towards the skin break up the fillet into manageable sections and do it slowly watch out for bones along the length of the middle spine if you feel or see any bones remove them once you&rsquo;re done scraping check to see if you missed out any bones if not put them aside.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
